# **IMRAN** ADEREMI

## Aspiring Software Developer

Imran.a.aderemi@gmail.com | +44 7576 843583 | linkedin.com/in/ImranAderemi | https://github.com/ImranAderemi

### **SUMMARY**

I'm an 18-year-old aspiring **Software Developer**, I'm extremely **goal-driven**, **hardworking**, **determined**, and **eager to learn**. I also have experience using **JavaScript**, **HTML5**, **CSS**, **C++**, **C#**, **Unreal Engine 4 & 5**, **Pseudocode**, **SQL/Excel**, **Python**. Seeking opportunities to gain work experience and learn valuable skills in a professional workplace setting.

#### **EDUCATION**

SEP 2022 - JUL 2024 (Completed)

B-TEC, WESTMINSTER KINGSWAY COLLEGE, LONDON, ENG

A 2-year course at Westminster Kingsway College where I graduated with an 'MMM' on a Level 3 National Extended Diploma in Information Technology.

SEP 2017 - AUG 2022 (Completed)

GCSES, WESTMINSTER CITY SCHOOL, L ONDON, ENG

I attended Westminster City School for 5 years and departed with 8 GCSEs all grade (9-4), Including **Computer Science**, Combined Sciences, English Language, English Literature and Maths.

### **EXPERIENCE**

11 MAR 2024 - 28 MAR 2024

INTERN WEB DEVELOPER, 21K DIGITAL MEDIA

A 2-week work placement with 21K Digital media, Where I focused on further developing my skills with **HTML**, **CSS**, and **JavaScript**. I worked on developing webpages for clients and also assisted in translating the clients brief to the team that would be developing it.

20 MAR 2023 – 31 MAR 2023

JUNIOR GAMES DEVELOPER, METROCALK

A 2-week placement where I practiced and developed my games development skills using Unreal Engine 4 and Unreal Engine 5. I spent time creating levels and mini projects and practicing how to exploit some of the features that were available.

## **AWARDS**

(November 2024 (Expected))

- FOUNDATIONAL C# CERTIFICATION, MICROSOFT/FREECODECAMP

January 2020 (Completed)

- Certificate of Distinction, UK Bebras Challenge 2020

# **TECHNOLOGY/SKILLS**

JavaScript, HTML5, CSS, C++, C#, Unreal Engine 4 & 5, Pseudocode, SQL/Excel, Python.